Aidan Tilgner

WEB DEVELOPER

aidantilgner02@gmail.com +1 (503) 200-7472 aidantilgner.dev linkedin.com/in/aidan-tilgner github.com/AidanTilgner

_

As a goal-oriented individual, I have taken strides towards a career in web development. In pursuit of this I have gained skills related to the field through project-oriented experience with web development technologies. I continue to learn more every day and intend to break into the industry soon as an asset to a company that fits my values. Those I would consider mentors have expressed that I am a driven, innovative, and improvement-obsessed person with an unending thirst to learn. I have also been told by those in the industry that my greatest strengths include my quick learning, ability to bring complex problems into smaller, more digestible pieces, and my communication skills in a team environment.

EXPERIENCE

Courtesy Clerk | Safeway

APRIL 2020 - Present

- Provided reliable customer support to clients by addressing all inquiries and informing them of product updates.
- Performed duties outside the job description including working in multiple departments in order to keep high-volume customer interaction and store operations running smoothly.
- Assisted the store director in keeping maintenance around the store and setting up new displays.

Bistro Specialist | B&G Bingo

APRIL 2018 - NOVEMBER 2020, Salem, OR

- Recorded customer orders while providing a positive customer experience.
- Collaborated with team members to prepare and serve meals to 300+ guests.

EDUCATION

BrainStation | Diploma Recipient, Web Development

FEB 2021 - MAY 2021, Remote

Over the course of around 450 total hours, I learned web development technologies, concepts, and best practices through a variety of sprint-based, professional-grade projects, taught by industry professionals.

Sprague High School | High School Diploma

SEP 2017 - JUNE 2021, Salem, OR

At my high school I took two, semester-long courses on basic web design and development, using JavaScript and Bootstrap. This pointed me in the direction of web development as a career.

SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript, React.js, MongoDB, Node.js, UI Design, Front End Design, Web Development

PROJECTS

GitHub - https://github.com/AidanTilgner

Portfolio - https://www.aidantilgner.dev/home

Soapbox - https://www.aidantilgner.dev/portfolio/#soapbox

InStock - https://www.aidantilgner.dev/porfolio